as everyone knows or should know this
Sunday is Mother's Day
right okay without a doubt without a
doubt the most important day of the year
my mom
watches no it is important so here's
what we did we sent out our nightly show
special contributor level Crawford to
see how people on the streets of New
York were prepping for the big
day this is the veil craw for the
nightly show and Mother's Day is coming
up I'm a mama's boy and I'm trying to
see who else loves their mama so I'm in
New York right now to find out do you
love your mama what are you getting your
mother for Mother's Day flowers
chocolates flowers and chocolate that's
it you and your mama don't have a good
relationship I'll do anything for my
mother oh yeah yeah oh yeah take a
bullet you see what
I mother mother mother mother I love
Mothers you know I think they're the
great they're the fruit of the tree
they're the fruit of life that's what
they told me but I don't know if I
believe it in three words name give me
give me your best description of your
mother she's strong she's independent
and she's artistic well you want to know
my three words about my mama better than
yours my mama can kick your mama's ass
any day oh she here hi hi I didn't know
that you were here I apologize she was
talking mess you didn't hear what she
said by my M for real what did your
daughter get you what was the nicest
gift she ever got you uh this Tiffany's
bracelet oh hell is what if you gotten
your mama for Mother's Day it's not the
material things I think the best gift
you can oh you full of crap now my
daughter was supposed to meet me today
cuz I'm going to my dentist she's going
to a gall of dinner she said can you
manage I can manage what's her name
Vicky Vicki where are you Liv in the
city where are you Vicky your mother is
talking to a strange black man cuz she
don't have nothing to do cuz you didn't
want to come and take her to the dentist
describe your mom and three words up
beautiful strong responsible well let me
describe my mama to you what better than
yours I don't know about all that my
mama KCK your mama ass I don't know
about all that why not your mama here y
she's right over there this
grandma look in the camera and tell your
mama how special she is to you all right
all right Mom I love you so much and
thank you for everything that you have
done for me and I'm a mama's boy ah that
is so beautiful I H you boy happy
Mother's day sweetheart I love you Mom
happy Mother's Day thank you very
much lville Crawford
everyone